https://foodofcourse.co.uk/privacy-policy-and-cookies/

Privacy Policy and Cookie Statement*** Please see important information about cookies and cookie control ***Who We AreFood of Course is a residential cookery school based in Sutton, Somerset. We are completely dedicated to providing all of our customers with clear transparent information about what we do and how we do it. This privacy policy is a natural extension of the honest and open way we do business. What Is The Purpose of This Policy?To let our customers and website visitors know the following:What personal data we collect when you visit our websiteHow we use your personal dataHow we make sure your privacy is maintainedYour legal rights regarding data collection, storage and deletionWhat cookies are, what cookies we use and what options you have to allow or disallow cookies on our website What Is Personal Data?Personal data is anything that discloses your identity; that is unique to you.For a more detailed breakdown of what constitutes personal data, please visit this page:https://eugdprcompliant.com What Personal Data Do We Collect?We collect personal data if you fill out a contact form, newsletter subscription form, or email us directly. Some plugins used on the site automatically collect data which is classified in the GDPR as 'Personal Data'.Personal Data - Enrolment Form, Contact Forms and EmailPersonal data we collect from direct emails or from our contact forms includes the following:First NameLast NameEmail AddressYou can unsubscribe from our mailing list at any time by contacting our data protection officer, Louise Hutton to request that you are removed from the mailing list.Date of birthAddressPhone NumberPersonal Data – Cookies, Analytics and PluginsSome plugins such as social media plugins, performance plugins (e.g. caching engines), and Google Analytics collect data via automated methods.The data collected by these plugins may include:Your IP address (An IP address is a number that can uniquely identify a specific computer or other network device on the internet).Browser typeSearch engine used (if applicable)System type (type of computer or device)The content and pages that you access on our websiteThe frequency and duration of your visits to our websiteThe “referring URL” (i.e., the page from which you navigated to our website)Cookie informationThe GDPR states that IP addresses should be considered personal data as they enter the scope of ‘online identifiers’.The information collected in this automated manner can be used to:Speed up performance and improve user experienceAnalyse your use of our websiteAllow users to like and share content on social mediaAnalyse our website's performance How Do We Use Your Personal Data?We use the information you give us to contact you directly about any genuine offers we have relating to our business or important news or information. Other data collected is used to analyse our website's performance and improve your user experience. Do We Share Your Data With Third Parties?Technically some of what the GDPR classifies as personal data collected by us is shared with third parties in conjunction with our mailing list, website analytics and our website’s functionality.Also, please see our note in Personal Data – Cookies, Analytics and Plugins about how IP addresses (classed by the GDPR as personal data) may be automatically collected and used by third party plugins on this website.We do not share your details with third parties for any purpose other than to provide you with direct marketing from us, to understand how you are using our website and to improve your user experience.We will never sell your data to any marketing companies. Data Security - Protecting Your PrivacyWe protect personal data with appropriate security.All of our data stored on computers is protected by technical security such as firewalls, anti-virus software and passwords.We understand the importance of data security and what procedures should be followed in case of a data security breach.Our website has an SSL certificate and powerful security software to protect and secure your connection.Our email clients are configured to use secure email connections.Security Breaches - Our Security ProcedureUnder GDPR law, if personal data has been put at risk we are required to report the breach to the Information Commissioners Office within 72 hours.Certain types of data breach do not need to be reported if they are considered harmless and poses no risk to individual data.If a breach is considered high-risk, we will inform all individuals who are impacted right away. We will do this via direct email or telephone depending on your contact preferences. Your Legal Rights Regarding Data Collection, Storage and DeletionThe GDPR includes the following rights for individuals or 'data subjects':The right to be informedThe right of accessThe right to rectificationThe right to erasureThe right to restrict processingThe right to data portabilityThe right to objectThe right not to be subject to automated decision-making including profiling Requests for Amendments, Copies or DeletionIf you would like us to update or delete any details we hold about you, or would like a copy of your personal data, simply send a request via email to louise.hutton@foodofcourse.co.ukIn accordance with the GDPR, any requests for amendments, deletion or copies of data will be fulfilled within 30 days (though usually much quicker). Embedded content from other websitesArticles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website. Links to Other Web SitesThis privacy policy is for this website only and does not cover any other sites that we link to. If you have questions about how another website uses your information, you’ll need to check that site’s privacy statement.CookiesCookie CategoriesHere are the cookie categories which this website may use:NecessaryNecessary cookies help make a website usable by enabling basic functions like page navigation and access to secure areas of the website. The website cannot function properly without these cookies.PreferencesPreference cookies enable a website to remember information that changes the way the website behaves or looks, like your preferred language or the region that you are in.StatisticsStatistic cookies help website owners to understand how visitors interact with websites by collecting and reporting information anonymously.MarketingMarketing cookies are used to track visitors across websites. The intention is to display ads that are relevant and engaging for the individual user and thereby more valuable for publishers and third party advertisers.UnclassifiedUnclassified cookies are cookies that we are in the process of classifying, together with the providers of individual cookies. Granting Us Permission to Use CookiesOur site uses cookies to enhance performance, security and user experience. We also use cookies to analyse how people use our website. As part of the GDPR, we need your permission to continue using these cookies. Please click the 'Okay' button on our Privacy Policy and Cookie Statement banner at the bottom of the page to give your consent. If you prefer not to use cookies, please see the links below for instructions on how to block them via your web browser.Mozilla FirefoxGoogle ChromeInternet ExplorerApple SafariMicrosoft EdgeNow that you have all the information you need to manage and delete cookies in your chosen browser, you can go forth and surf in the pleasure of knowing you have full control.If you have any questions or concerns about your privacy or any of the settings on this website, please contact us at any time.Contact UsLet the culinary fun begin!Ensure your place on our next fabulous cooking adventure at Food of Course cookery school.Enrol TodayGet in touchlouise.hutton@foodofcourse.co.uk+44 (0) 1749 860116Quick LinksHomeEnrolmentDates and FeesFind UsMiddle Farm House,Sutton, Shepton Mallet,Somerset, BA4 6QFContact UsPrivacy Policy & CookiesTerms & Conditions© Food of Course 2020 - all rights reserved | designed by
Lanx World
envelope-ohomemap-markercalendarphonepencilpaper-plane
This site uses cookies. Please click 'Okay' to accept or for more info see our privacy policy & cookies statement.Okay
